Kayro Valero Web Developer



Email

sannelvalero@gmail.com



Linkedin

linkedin.com/in/kayro-valero/

Web developer with +2 years of experience creating websites for e-Commerce, landing pages. I master programming languages such as HTML, CSS, PHP, and JavaScript. I have notable experience in WordPress,

and I am also capable of managing databases (MariaDB shell and MySQL). Additionally, I have skills in copywriting and SEO to create

compelling and effective web content. I am committed to providing



GitHub

github.com/kayro-svg

PROFILE





Soft Skills

Teamwork	87%
Skills	
Problem - Solving	96%
Flexibility and adaptability	90%
adapiability	
Critical	90%
thinking	
Effective	97%
communication	
Creativity	99%
Results-	90%

Digital & Language Skills

Adobe Photoshop	75%
Figma ———	80%
English (C1 Proficient)	75%



EXPERIENCE

2019 - Present

Applied Case Studies.

Web Designer & Developer

• Programming in HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript.

comprehensive solutions for web development needs.

- Management of relational databases (MySQL, MariaDB).
- IT project management.
- Development of Landing Pages and websites, and querying databases through programming with PHP.

Dic, 2022

Zona Sur AutoPartes Company

Web Designer & Developer on WordPress

- Development of a website using WordPress, Elementor, Woocommerce, and various plugins.
- SEO optimization.
- Graphic design.
- Development of e-commerce.

2020 - 2022

Cooperativa
Desarrollo Pesquero,
R.L. (Cooperative
Enterprise)

Executive Assistant | Copywriter | Social Media Manager

- Management and drafting of legal documents.
- Email and newsletter management.
- Writing, graphic design, advertising, and digital marketing for social media.
- Articles with SEO optimization for blogs.

EDUCATION

2021 - 2023

Universidad Autónoma de Chiriquí, Panamá.

2018 - 2020

Universidad Autónoma de Chiriquí, Panamá.

2023

Courses and selfdirected learning.

Bachelor's degree in Information Technology Management, Information Technology.

· Currently in the final semester of the degree.

Higher Technician Degree in Business Programming,

Information Technology.

Online courses.

- Python (In progress). Data Analysis (In progress).
- React (In progress)
 SEO optimization (In progress).